way2tnpsc.com 2019-08-03

# Privacy Policy - way2tnpsc.com

**PRIVACY POLICY**  
We are very grateful to you for visiting our way2tnpsc.com.Our website assures your privacy. We will not collect any personal information or details about you, unless you choose to afford your information needed to us. This privacy policy governs the privacy terms of our Website, located at http://way2tnpsc.com as owned and operated by WEBFALCON TECHNOLOGIES. We describe this privacy statement just to let you know how we communicate, collect or disclose your information. Here your email address or any personal information about you is not identified unless you login to our site. If you chooses to provide us any personal information e.g: your email address that will be used only to respond to your inquiry and notify you of any updates in our website. We will not distribute this information to any organization. 

**PERSONAL INFORMATION**  
We will secure your personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, usage or modifying as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying. Do remember that no data transmitted over internet is 100% secure. But we took our best effort to secure your information. As a visitor, you can browse our website without providing any information. 

**INFORMATION WE COLLECT**  
You are not mandatory to provide us with any of your Personally Identifiable Information as a Viewer. We collect only your name, e-mail ID to send you notifications. You can also ignore or control the information you provide to us by not logging in into our website. Without your knowledge and consent, we don’t collect any of your related content. 

**SYSTEM COLLECTED INFORMATION**  
When you visit our website, web server automatically collects your domain, IP address, proxy server, volume, date and time, pages you visit during the access. We are not responsible for such system related which is considered as non-personal information. 

**AUTOMATIC INFORMATION**  
We will automatically receive information about your location i.e.city from where you access and the pages you visit, name of the website from which you entered our site. You can turn off your location services in settings. The operating system you use, type of device, name of the mobile device, website provider, date and time you spend on each page of our site, your computer’s Internet protocol(“IP”) address, type of device you use to access our way2tnpsc are automatically collected information which is common in all websites. We will never sell or disclose your location to any of our other users. 

**LINKS**  
We have links to other sites. Please be aware that way2tnpsc.com are not responsible for any privacy practices of such sites.  Links we provide is just to make users comfortable so that they can find an easy way for that related content which they search. You can access those linked websites at your own risk. You can check their individual privacy policy which are not subject to our policy. 

**ADVERTISEMENTS**  
We serve ads for third-parties in our website. We are not responsible if such ads collects any of your relevant information. So do know that when you click on such advertisements, your information may or may not be collected by them. And we will not disclose any data about our users at any cost to any advertisement sites. 

**COOKIES**  
Cookies placed on your device when you browse improves our website to be efficient and free to use and also personalize the data that you able to view in way2tnpsc.com. It also helps to share our pages in social networks. Strictly, no sensitive or personal information is collected through cookies without your consent. If you wish, you can deactivate your cookies in your browser. However, if you disable cookies, you cannot able to view all the updated functionalities or modifications done in our website. Your privacy is important to us.   
Your privacy is important to us.
